http://www.artificialplants.co.uk/privacy-policy-i4

X
This site uses cookies to provide and improve your shopping experience.
If you want to benefit from this improved service, please opt-in.
More Info
I opt-in to a better browsing experience
Accept Cookies
Covid-19, We are still trading, but delivery times will vary due to the virus
Bay
View All Topiary & Bay»
Artificial Boxwood & Buxus
»
Artificial Cedar, Cypress & Juniper
»
Artificial Bay Topiary
»
Artificial Topiary Spirals
»
Artificial Topiary Balls
»
Artificial Lollipop Topiary Trees
Hanging Baskets
View All Hanging Baskets»
Artificial Hanging Baskets & Window Box Displays
»
Artificial Christmas Items!
Plants & Grasses
View All Plants & Grasses»
Artificial Cactus
»
Artificial Garlands and Artificial Trailing Plants
»
Artificial Spiky Plants
»
Artificial Indoor Plants
»
Artificial Ivy
»
Artificial Outdoor Plants
»
Artificial Flame Proof Plants
»
Artificial Flowering Plants
»
Artificial Succulents
»
Artificial Grass Plants
»
Artificial Herbs
Flowers &Foliage
View All Flowers &Foliage»
Artificial Hand Tied Bouquets
»
Artificial Foliage
»
Arrangements & Floral Gifts
»
Artificial Flower Stems
»
Artificial Peonies
Hedging & Screening
View All Hedging & Screening»
Artificial Hedging & Screens
»
Artificial Christmas Items!
Artificial living walls & Moss
View All Artificial living walls & Moss»
Artificial Living Walls & Moss
»
Artificial Christmas Items!
Planters
View All Planters»
Pots & Troughs
»
Artificial Christmas Items!
Inc. VAT Ex. VAT
Free Shipping
On Orders Over £100!
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThe Artificial Plants Shop cares about protecting your data and privacy. This policy is to inform you of how we use and store your personal data. How your Information is used.Your information and data will always be used and stores with confidentiality to provide and maintain service. Here are the specific ways we may use your information.Administer your accountDisplay relevant contentInternal Research & AnalysisInternal Marketing Service - Newsletters etc Data Collected When OrderingPersonal data is collected to process your order. We will not release your name, address, email address or any other information about you to any outside party save to regulatory authorities as required by law.  Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive completely confidential.this will only ever be used solely for internal purposes. We will not share your personal information with any other parties, and we only use cookies to facilitate your order process. If you are concerned about your personal data, you have the right to request access to personal data which we hold or process about you. You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge.At any point please contact us to opt-out of your data being used for internal marketing from the artificial plants shop. You can also do this in the My Account tab on the website.Accessing The Data We HoldShould you wish to access a copy of the personal you have provided is (Know as a Subject Access Request) You may do so by emailing or calling our customer care team who will take you through some security to gain access. We will respond to your request ASAP and always within the statutory 30days. Should we require more information from you to verify your identity to ensure we provide the date to the rightful person the 30 days will start once the information if provided.Storing Your InformationThe information you provided us we will store for no longer than is legally required.Sharing of Your Information With Third PartiesAs part of marketing and delivering the best service we may use carefully selected third parties to process services on our behalf. This would not be for marketing their own products or services. You may request a copy of our third parties by emailing sales@artificialplants.co.uk
x
Join
Compare (1)
Top
